During the Pre-Impossible Mission Planning
The time is 2 p.m., and Mr. Uwe is in the drawing room.
The assassin's made their way into the manor
disguised as a deliveryman.
They have a weapon concealed in their pocket.
Let me think...
I start by having Sara's animals
check them for firearms.
They aren't carrying anything that
smells of gunpowder.
The assassin advances.
I station Lily and Sybilla on the
left and right to stand guard.
The assassin turns the corner and
enters their blind spot.
They kill a nearby maid.
You lose your bead on their location.
That wasn't bad.
Let's go again.
Are you up for it?
Yes, of course.
By the way, I have a question...
The panties I'm wearing today are white.
That wasn't what I was going to ask.
You really didn't have to finish that sentence.
Just as I expected.
I was actually hoping to ask about
something more serious.
Serious how?
Why weren't you able to take advantage of
your talents back at your academy?
I have everyone's test scores and evaluations.
Everyone else has logical reasons
for why they washed out.
However, you're the one person
I don't have a good explanation for.
What happened?
I doubt you would believe me if I told you.
I promise to accept whatever you tell me.
I really appreciate that.
The truth is,
I'm not good with men.
Boss?
I'm sorry, I'm afraid I don't follow.
Being around men makes my stomach start hurting.
You seem fine around me, though.
You're an exception, Boss.
Well, that seems awfully convenient.
That's fine, though.
I did promise to accept your explanation.
That love of yours is a mysterious thing.
Is it?
In that case, I have a question for you as well.
Where did you get that cut on your hand?
I had an urgent mission this afternoon,
and embarrassingly, I got it caught on something.
Your fatigue is starting to get you hurt.
Please, you should go to bed.
Don't worry about it.
Besides, I have a backlog of reports
I need to get through.
I'm not giving this fountain pen back
until you get some sleep.
Magnificent.
Very well, I'll turn in for the night.
You can go ahead and-
Of course, I'll get in bed with you
and sing you a lullaby.
Get out.
You must be tired too.
I'll be asleep soon,
so please get the lights on your way-
That was fast.
Did you let your guard down because
it was me you were with?
Have you come to want to let me dote on you,
even just a little?
I'm under no illusions about my love ever bearing fruit.
But even so,
once I complete the mission and make you proud,
would it be greedy of me to hope for
just one percent of your affection?
SPY CLASSROOM
Itami ga unda daishou
Nido to kienai kasabuta wo dakishime
Gouin na sukimakaze ano hi sarawareta
Kawarenai boku wa oiteikanakucha
Nee fuan sae oikoshite
Shiranakatta sora to kyou wa kono ashi de
Chouyou wo mukaeyou
Fukou ga kureta shiawase
Zetsubou no hate ni mieta
Shirube wa ima hitosuji no hi wo tomosu
Karamiau kako wo harae
Kokoro ga hokorobu basho made aragau
Ah, shunkan ikinobiro
MISSION: Daughter Dearest III
Tomorrow evening,
there's going to be a dinner party at the mansion.
The attendees are just going to be politicians
and other political bigwigs who share Mr. Uwe's views,
but we need to be prepared for anything
that might happen.
Sara, I need you to keep watch over
the mansion starting tonight.
Will do.
Now, what can you tell me about
the incident the other night?
Sadly, there weren't any clues in the traps we set.
This little guy couldn't even pick up the bad guy's scent,
so they must have come prepared.
I see.
B-by the way,
do you think there's a chance the assassin
will come back tomorrow?
It's a possibility,
which is why we're staying on high alert.
R-right...
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I'm ready to give it my all!
That's reassuring to hear.
I have instructions from the boss:
"Chisel Mr. Uwe like you were chiseling
a rock from the bottom of the sea."
What's that in normal-person talk?
I believe he wants you to get Uwe to tell you details
about the people who'll be
attending the function tomorrow.
On it.
What's good, Uwe?
We should start thinkin' about heading out, yeah?
It's an hour earlier than usual.
Yeah, but the weather's not gonna hold.
Besides, if we get there early,
you can tell me all about the people
who'll be comin' tomorrow.
I'm going to go plant more bugs around
the mansion to get ready for the party.
Lily, would you mind distracting the
other residents for me while I do?
Leave it to me!
I figured you'd ask, so I actually already knocked over
a bucket and soaked the hallway downstairs.
I think I might've developed a knack for precognition-
Shoot! I didn't think she'd find it 'til later!
Who did this?! Who poured water everywhere?!
Lily's bold moves make for a perfect diversion.
Everything's going smoothly.
The Next Day
No intruders.
I went through the pockets of
everyone who seemed sketchy,
but none of 'em had any weapons.
Sara didn't see anything out of the ordinary, either.
And Lily even got through her maid work
without screwing up for a change.
Probably 'cuz your instructions were so dang good.
Oh, not at all.
If anything, I should be the one complimenting you all.
I spent the entire party hiding away in the back.
By the way, Grete,
you said you came from a politician's family, right?
I did. What about it?
Did you spend a bunch of time at
high society shindigs like this one?
I'm kinda jealous.
It's like, it's all so swanky.
Not quite.
I never could find a place for myself in this world.
That so?
Grete!
Could I speak with you?
Why'd you spend the whole party over in the kitchen?
I wanted you out on the floor mingling with the guests.
My deepest apologies.
I wasn't feeling well,
but I figured I could at least help by
washing dishes and cleaning up.
The world of politics is dominated by men, you know.
Having a couple of cute young maids going
around with smiles on their faces
helps make parties like ours run that much smoother.
I see.
So, what's the deal?
Did you just feel like slacking off?
If I tell her that I have problems dealing with men,
she'll see me as unfit to be a maid,
and she might even fire me.
That said, the more lies I pile on, the more likely
my whole story is to eventually fall apart.
Grete?
T-to tell you the truth,
there's someone I'm quite in love with,
so getting close to other men doesn't-
That changes everything!
Spill, girl!
I-if you insist.
It's what you would call lovesickness.
When I think of him, it makes me
not want to talk to other men.
Oh, was it that guy from the other day?
I saw Sybilla and Lily talking to a total hunk
right after the assassin attacked.
Skinny guy, long hair!
No, someone else.
That man's just a teacher from our school.
I suspect he was just dropping by
his students' job site to check in on us.
He's not the guy, huh?
Can I have him, then?
Huh?
I mean, a schoolteacher like him?
He's probably all kinds of pent up.
All I'd have to do is get some drinks in him and pretend
to be tipsy so I could press my chest against him,
and I could get him into bed and
let nature take its course.
Would you look at that?
You can make faces like that after all.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Look, I've got nothing against lovesickness,
just make sure it doesn't get in the way of your job.
Besides, men flock to good-looking gals like us.
You don't have to take life so seriously.
Needy women don't get loved.
I despise that philosophy.
I can't stand people who don't put in the work
to be worthy of love.
Excuse me?
Isn't that right there the reason nobody loves you?
Oh, I hit the nail on the head.
We're done here.
The room feels darker just having you in it.
If you look like you're fighting back
a grimace the whole time,
you'll just bring down the mood
at the parties anyways.
By your leave, then.
That was made in Galgad.
That's a very pretty brooch.
It was a present from my boyfriend.
What about it?
Nothing, I was just saying.
I'm so tired.
Isn't that right there the reason nobody loves you?
I know that.
How could I not?
I never got a chance to give it back.
Boss...
Hello?
Long day, huh?
Lily? Did something-
Nah, you just stay right where you are.
Pat, pat...
Um...
You looked super tired,
so I thought I'd pamper you a bit.
Sorry it's my hands and not Teach's.
Dang, you've got all kinds of knots.
It makes sense, though,
considering the unreal amount of work you're doing.
You're giving me too much credit.
And she's humble, to boot!
You have a very impressive figure, Lily.
Where's this coming from?!
I've tried to seduce the boss so many times,
but the constant failures are
starting to make me nervous.
Nah, c'mon, don't beat yourself up about it.
I mean, your figure is plenty...
Uh...
Plenty what?
Plenty good for crossdressing with.
Th-that's our resident master of disguise for you.
She's such an expert, she doesn't even need
a chest binder to pass as a man!
Why, it's basically like she's
crossdressing twenty-four-seven!
Would it be all right if I broke your pinky finger?
You're that pissed?!
Don't you worry.
There're loads of charming things about you.
That's why no matter what happens,
we'll always be friends.
I find it hard to imagine there being
anything charming about me at all.
Who would ever love a girl like you?!
Why can't you even smile like a normal person?!
Why was I burdened with a daughter
as creepy as you?!
Androphobia, huh?
Her father all but forced her to enroll in her academy.
The official story is that she's living overseas
as part of the treatment for some illness.
In other words, her politician father
basically abandoned her.
It says here she chose the code name
Daughter Dearest herself,
but I'm sure there are plenty of things these
scraps of paper can't possibly tell me about her.
Now, it's high time we started...
this assassin hunt of ours.
MISSION: Daughter Dearest III
This is a list of the politicians we suspect
were killed by Corpse.
Corpse's primary MO is making it look like
the victims committed suicide
by jumping to their deaths.
It doesn't use weapons, so it's hard to trace.
There are probably all loads
of other assassinations
that have been written off as suicides
that we just don't know about.
That's so messed up.
Many of the dead politicians were people
who devoted everything they had
to getting our nation back on its feet after the war.
Losing them hurts.
So, this is why they call it a shadow war.
Sara...
Don't worry.
As the World's Strongest,
I'll make sure I put Corpse down.
There's no need to be so afraid.
I-I have to tell you!
I know it's pathetic,
but hearing that made me feel better.
I'm glad you've started relying on us,
but if I'm being totally honest, I feel a lot safer
when I know you're protecting us.
That's nothing to be ashamed of.
But, um, that's why I think you should
pay more attention to Miss Grete.
I don't know if you realize just how much courage
it takes her to do what she's doing.
Duly noted.
Uwe!
Damn you, killer!
What the hell do you think you're doin', dumbass?!
You should know that
givin' your opponent a clear shot
is about the most dangerous thing you can do.
R-right.
You hurt?
Not a scratch.
And it's all thanks to you, White.
When you moved my bed away from the window,
it made it into a blind spot.
I was able to escape his shots unscathed.
Dang, that was a lucky-ass coincidence.
I saw him.
It was that man with the hideous birthmark.
You actually got a good look at him?
My eyes have gotten a lot better
since you lot started cooking for me.
The next time he shows it will be
the day he meets his maker.
Look, you wanna think about hiring a security guard?
This guy's shown up twice in a single week.
No price is too high
when it comes to keepin' your family safe.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Welcoming more outsiders into the house
can't possibly be a good idea,
not when you have no idea who the assassin might be.
I'm terrified at the very thought.
B-but...
If anything, shouldn't you think about firing
the intruders who only just got here?
What the hell are you on about?
Who do you think it was that saved Uwe just-
You know, you don't seem frightened by any of this.
Neither do the other two.
You were so brave during the first attack.
Are you used to things like this?
Why is that?
Was you moving the bed really just a coincidence?
Uwe, don't you think we should look into
the girls' backgrounds again?
For example, we could start with a thorough
inspection of their personal effects.
You can't...
Just so you know, Olivia...
it's dangerous to pick up glass with your bare hands.
Glass?
You're so right!
I cut my finger a little.
I need to go wash up.
When did Olivia grab that glass shard?
If she had wanted to, she could've-
Sybilla, please focus on your maid work for now.
Say, what's that punk Klaus got to say about all this?
He says to leave everything to me.
He really trusts you that much?
Also, where is he even?
Sybilla, I'll handle the cleanup in here.
Would you mind taking Uwe to another room?
Y-you got it.
I have the situation under control.
The enemy is starting to show their true colors.
I need to start making preparations for the showdown.
From here on out,
I can't afford to make a single mistake.
If I screw up...
I'll revise the plan as many times as it takes.
I just need a little more time...
Are you okay, Grete?
I-I'm terribly sorry.
My foot slipped a little, but I'm fine now.
No, you're not.
You need another massage.
I'm gonna knead you up until your whole
body's as mushy as a jellyfish.
Y-you really don't...
M-may I ask...
Tricked you.
Secure the target!
Wh-what exactly are you doing?
Enemies are to be brutally interrogated.
Wh-what do you plan on doing with that?
Here, we show our enemies no mercy.
B-but yesterday, you said we would always be friends.
I was fibbing.
Don't you think there are some lies
you really shouldn't tell?
If you thought we were gonna be the ones
getting conned forever...
then you were dead wrong.
A listening device?
When did you...
So, the guy with the birthmark...
That was secretly you in disguise, wasn't it?
I surrender.
You're right, it was me all alon-
This is so much fun!
So, why'd you do it?
I-I was about to tell you, but then you distracted me!
Your reactions are so cute, I couldn't help myself.
I disguised myself as the assassin
so could watch how any maids and guards reacted.
That way, I could see if any of them
had undergone special training.
Don't you think it's time you looped us in?
What's this mission really about?
But...
You're incredible, Grete.
In the end, none of the rest of us were able to tell
the boss that we wanted to share his burden.
But now, I'll say this:
I want to share your burden, Grete.
Ditto to that.
Me too.
All right...
Please listen, everyone.
Our target, Corpse, is actually-
I figured you kids were operatives.
Well, fine, we can ditch the subtlety this time.
Get to the window!
Round two!
Mr. Bernard!
MR. BERNARD!
Where's Teach?!
We need to get him here, fast!
He's not here.
The boss won't be coming for us.
This is a battle we have to win on our own.
Furishikiru yoru o zutto nagameteta
Doredake chikazuitemo
(Give it up, give it up)
Himitsu no namae sotto watasetara
Mitsukaranai you ni kurayami ni toketeiku
Kossori naiteta koto mo wasurechatta
Saibou ga irekawatta mitai
Betsu no hito ni nattari
Isogashii hibi motto fuzakeyou ne
Chotto kimi to hanashitai kedo
Daremo mou inai
Yakusokuda nante
Sonna mono janai deshou
Furishikiru yoru o zutto nagameteta
Doredake chikazuitemo
(Give it up, give it up)
Himitsu no namae sotto watasetara
Mitsukaranai you ni kurayami ni toketeiku
Soshite umarekawatte
Massara na yozora wo tobimawatte
Nando mo kousa kimi to watashi
Suihei na hoshi ni tatte
Masugu na hitomi de mitsumeatte
Mata aeta toki ni watashitai yo